

Yuri K Product Designer

LANGUAGES

English - B1

WHO AM I?

Hi, I'm Yuri, a UX/UI Designer. I specialize in Product Design, User Experience (UX),UI Design, Web Interfaces Design, Wireframing. I think the design should be very informative. So, I pay special attention to creating an interactive prototype. I'm working with Figma, Illustrator, Photoshop, Lightroom, After Effects. My life motto is "Any difficulties are just tasks that I can solve".

SKILLS

 Figma
 Usability Testing
 User Experience Design
 UX/UI Prototyping
 UX/UI Design
 Wireframing

 Low-Fi Prototyping
 Product Design
 Webflow

EDUCATION

Sochi State University

Bachelor's degree in Applied Computer Science.

EXPERIENCE

2021 — 2021 **UX/UI Designer**

Product Design

Help design an MVP car rental service. Design of the main user flow, creation of a low-fi prototype. https://www.behance.net/gallery/142959237/Car-rent-service-prototype

UX/UI Prototyping UX/UI Design Low-Fi Prototyping Wireframing

2022 — 2022 Product Designer

A web portal where people can create and store their resumes. The portal provides an opportunity to create custom skills and send resumes to the customer. I have developed the entire design of the portal and created adaptive versions for mobile devices. Created an interactive prototype of the interface, conducted usability testing. https://www.behance.net/gallery/142962943/CVs-Storage

Wireframing Low-Fi Prototyping Product Design Usability Testing

User Experience Design User Interface Design

2022 — Present UX/UI Designer

Development of the website of a Software Development Company. Development of the concept and structure of the site. Work with custom illustrations and animation. https://www.behance.net/gallery/142961929/Company-landing-page

UX/UI Design UX/UI Prototyping Wireframing